harristeeter.com 2014-07-01

# Harris Teeter - Privacy Policy

**Harris Teeter’s Privacy Policy**

Harris Teeter is committed to protecting the privacy and security of any personal information you provide to us, including your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, credit card information, and checking account information. Our Privacy Policy sets out our policies and practices for collecting, maintaining, using, sharing, and protecting your personal information.

You may choose to share personal information with Harris Teeter by participating in Harris Teeter’s VIC ® program or in various promotions and sweepstakes, by visiting our Web site, by making purchases in our stores using personal checks or credit or debit cards, by making special requests for items not found in our stores, or by using the services of our pharmacies, among other ways.

[Click here to learn more about Harris Teeter's public wireless policy.](http://www.harristeeter.com/in_our_stores/in_store_services/public_wifi_policy.aspx)

**How Your Information Is Collected and Used**  
If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may use that information to provide you with products or services that you have requested, to investigate and answer questions or concerns that you submit to us, to create promotional programs or offers tailored to you, to list you as a winner of a contest or sweepstakes, when appropriate, or to notify you of other information of interest regarding Harris Teeter. 

Harris Teeter will never sell any personal customer information. Harris Teeter, its affiliates and business partners may use personal customer information to create merchandising and promotional programs tailored to you. This information usage is for purposes such as analyzing and aggregating our data, implementing and managing marketing campaigns and initiatives, filling requests or orders you place with us, providing customer service, hosting our Web servers, and processing payments. Harris Teeter requires all affiliates and business partners to maintain strict confidentiality, except as specifically set forth in this policy. Harris Teeter also collects and uses aggregate data that do not contain personally identifiable information, such as demographic or statistical information, which we may share with third parties.

When you visit our Web site, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a “cookie” to identify you and enhance your experience on the site. Cookies are small files placed on your computer’s hard drive. They are used for a variety of reasons, such as remembering user names and passwords and preferences and tracking click streams. By using cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized experience on our Web site. Your browser gives you the option to reject cookies, but doing so generally hinders the browser’s performance and will adversely affect your experience when using our Web site. We may collect certain technical information from your computer when you visit our Web site, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type, and any referring Web site address. We use this information for enhancing your visits to our site and for system administration, security, and troubleshooting. 

**Third-Party Web Sites**  
Harris Teeter’s Web site provides links to third-party Web sites, so that we can offer additional goods, services, and information to you. Any personal information you provide when accessing a third party’s Web site is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We do not control the use of the information you provide to third parties, and we assume no responsibility for your sharing of information with them. 

**When Your Information May Be Disclosed**  
Harris Teeter will disclose personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires us to do so. Harris Teeter also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information when we believe disclosure is necessary to respond to claims against us, to protect our customers, to ensure the integrity and operation of our business, or to protect the rights, property, and best interests of Harris Teeter, its affiliates, or others.

**Pharmacy Records**  
Harris Teeter takes special precautions with your pharmacy records. We follow the federal guidelines set by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). [Additional information on Harris Teeter’s privacy policy for pharmacy records](http://www.harristeeter.com/in_our_stores/departments/pharmacy/hipaa_privacy_policy/hipaa_privacy_policies.aspx).

**Children’s Privacy**  
Harris Teeter takes special precautions with children’s privacy. We follow the federal guidelines set by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not actively seek personal information about children under the age of 13 without the permission of their parent or legal guardian. We do not provide personal information about children to any third-party, other than in accordance with other sections of this privacy policy. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe that child has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, you may contact us to review and request deletion of the information and prohibit its use, using the contact information below.

**Strict Security Measures**  
Harris Teeter enforces strict security measures to prevent the disclosure of your personal information without your consent. We maintain a security system that encrypts personal information you enter online while it is being transmitted over the Internet. We also maintain employee policies that mandate protection of your personal information.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us in one of the following ways: 

  * By calling us, at 1-800-432-6111 
  * By visiting www.harristeeter.com and selecting the “Contact Us” link/button 
  * By writing to us at Harris Teeter, Inc., Attn: Customer Relations, P.O. Box 10100, Matthews, NC 28106-0100 

You may request changes to your personal information by contacting us as shown above. You must provide proof of your identity to make such changes.

You may also access your own personal purchasing information by contacting us in writing, as shown above.

If you provide us with your personal information but later decide you no longer want us to use that information, let us know by contacting us as shown above.

**This Policy May Change**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 17, 2010. We may update the Privacy Policy whenever new developments in business, technology, law, or regulation, call for changes. Any updates will be made by posting a revised policy on the Harris Teeter Web site. This Privacy Policy is not intended to create any contractual or other legal rights in, or on behalf of, any person or entity.

Copyright © 2010 Harris Teeter
